Harrison Hadaway

harrisonleehadaway@gmail.com 662.574.7221

Web Development

120 E Main St Apt 1705 Lexington, KY 40507

Summary

Since I began a 3-month full-stack web development bootcamp in September, I have been intrigued by teams coming together to complete web development projects. I finished bootcamp in December 2017 and have an ultimate career goal of being in project management. My background includes a variety of industries, but the common factor throughout my previous work experience is my passion for working with people.

Education

Awesome Inc U / Bootcamp Alumnus

August 2017 - December 2017, Lexington, KY

The Web Developer Bootcamp is a 3-month, full-time training program for individuals looking to jumpstart a career in web development. During this intense training program, I gained experience while building projects with HTML, CSS, Javascript, Gulp, PHP, VueJS, Laravel, Git, Github, AWS S3, and Heroku. HarrisonHadaway.com

East Mississippi Community College / AAS - Electrical Technology

August 2011 - December 2015, Mayhew, MS

Studies included a core of liberal arts classes with a focus on technical electrical technology. Studies included blueprint reading and drawing, residential, commercial, and industrial best practices, electrical theory, AC/DC circuits, programmable logic controllers and electric motor drives, with all classes being taught with an emphasis on safety.

Experience

Bolin Farms / Farm Manager

January 2017 - August 2017, Holly Springs, MS

Bolin Farms is privately-owned and is located across the state of Mississippi. I was the key contact and utility employee for the out-of-state owners, traveling weekly between properties to ensure proper maintenance of land, farm equipment and vehicles. While at Awesome Inc U, I created an Equipment Tracker app that will be used by Bolin Farms in 2018. equipment-tracker.net

Prince Newspapers / Digital Media Coordinator

July 2016 - December 2016, Philadelphia, MS

Prince Newspapers serves three markets in Mississippi. My responsibility was to introduce digital marketing to small and traditionally print-only advertisers in the Philadelphia, MS area by holding needs analysis meetings, presenting digital products and serving accounts once active.

Amptech Electric / Electrician

March 2016 - June 2016, Macon, MS

Amptech is an electrical contractor specializing in commercial, agricultural, and industrial electrical installation, maintenance and troubleshooting. When I was not out working with the crew, I rebuilt the company's website. amptechelectric.net

Noxubee Medical Complex / IT Specialist

January 2012 - May 2013, Macon, MS

A county owned Medical Complex consisting of a critical access hospital, nursing home, and 3 medical clinics. I was hired as the second employee of the IT department amongst their first implementation of an electronic health record system. My role was focused on hardware, network and end-user support and training.